[
    {
        "question": "Aa",
        "answer": "A is for Apple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bb",
        "answer": "B is for Ball"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Cc",
        "answer": "C is for Cake"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Dd",
        "answer": "D is for Duck"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Ee",
        "answer": "E is for Egg"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Ff",
        "answer": "F is for Fish"

    },
    {
        "question": "Gg",
        "answer": "G is for Giraffe"
       
    },
    {
        "question": "Hh",
        "answer": "H is for Heart"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Ii",
        "answer": "I is for Ice Cream"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Jj",
        "answer": "J is for Jellyfish"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Kk",
        "answer": "K is for Key"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Ll",
        "answer": "L is for Lemon"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Mm",
        "answer": "M is for Moon"
    
    },
    {
        "question": "Nn",
        "answer": "N is for Number"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Oo",
        "answer": "O is for Orange"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pp",
        "answer": "P is for Pig"
    },
    {
        "question": "Qq",
        "answer": "Q is for Queen"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Rr",
        "answer": "R is for Robot"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Ss",
        "answer": "S is for Sun"
        
    },
    {
        "question": "Tt",
        "answer": "T is for Turtle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Uu",
        "answer": "U is for Umbrella"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vv",
        "answer": "V is for Violin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ww",
        "answer": "W is for Watermelon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Xx",
        "answer": "X is for Xylophone"
    },
    {
        "question": "Yy",
        "answer": "Y is for Yarn"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zz",
        "answer": "Z is for Zebra"
    }
]